(Sheldon:)It is only by opening the box
that you'll find out which it is.
(Penny:)Okay, so you're saying
I should go out with Leonard?
(Leonard:)No, no, no.
(Sheldon:)Let me start again.
In 1935, Erwin Schrödinger...
(Leonard(pointing):)Two seats right there.
[SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I think I've made a mistake.
(Sheldon:)I can see that.
Unless you're running a marathon...
(Sheldon:)...choosing both stuffing and mashed
potatoes is a starch-filled redundancy.
(Leonard:)No, it's about Penny.
(Sheldon:)A mistake involving Penny.
(Sheldon:)Okay, you'll have to narrow it down.
(Leonard:)I don't think
I can go out with her tonight.
(Sheldon:)Then don't.
Other people would say, "Why not?"
(Sheldon:)Other people might be interested.
- I'm gonna talk anyway.
- I assumed you would.